<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="Joke">
        <item>Boy 1: Why do you run from a naked lady?\nBoy 2: Becos my mum said that if I look at a naked lady, I’ll turn into stone. A part of me is getting hard already!</item>
        <item>Sex is like a restaurant.Sometimes you get full satisfactory service, and sometimes you have to be satisfied with self-service”</item>
        <item>What makes a happy man?\nDaughter on the cover of cosmo.\nSon on the cover of sports illustrated.\nMistress on the cover of playboy\nand ..\nWife on the cover of “missing persons”\n</item>
        <item>Why was the 2-piece swimsuit invented?\nTo separate the HAIRY section from the DAIRY section.\n</item>
        <item>Teacher: What do you want to become?\nLittle Johnny: Doctor !!\nTeacher: Why?\nLittle Johnny: Coz its the only profession where u can tell a woman to take off her clothes and ask her husband to pay for it.</item>
        <item>Woman complaining to dentist: “It’s so painful, I’ll rather have a baby than have a tooth removed.”\nDentist: “Make up your mind soon,I ll adjust the chair accordingly.”</item>
        <item>Old lady, 85, a virgin, about to die. wanted her tombstone to read :\nBORN A VIRGIN, LIVED A VIRGIN, DIED A VIRGIN.\nThe engraver shortened it to: ” RETURNED UNOPENED ”</item>
        <item>75 yr old man got married to a 15 yr girl.\nOn their first night\nboth were crying - why???\nCoz she didn’t know anything, and he had forgotten everything</item>
        <item>Judge: you want to divorce your husband for threatening you with a deadly weapon?\nWife: no ur honor i am divorcing him for threatening of every night with dead weapon.</item>
        <item>2 men went 2 a callgirl.\n1st went in and came out n said:“Na my wife is better.”\n2nd went in and came out n said:“U R right ur wife is much better.”</item>
        <item>How are women and tornadoes alike?\nThey both moan like hell when they come, and take the house when they leave.</item>
        <item>Man marries deaf Girl-He writes-We must fix a Code: If I want SEX I`ll press ur left BooB-U reply by shakin my penis once for YES, or 50 times for NO....!</item>
        <item>Two prostitutes were talking: We`re in the best business in the world\nWhy`s that then?\nWell, we`ve got it, we sell it, and we`ve STILL got it!</item>
        <item>Little Boy: Dad How Was I Born\nDad: Well, Son Ur Mom and I Got Together at `Yahoo`.\nWe Set up A Date Via E-Mail and Met In Cyber Cafe Ur Mom Agreed To `Download..... Data` From My `Pen Drive`.\nJust When I Was About to Transfer, We Realised That Non Of Us Had Installed A Firewall It Was Too Late To hit Delete.\nNine Months Later A Pop-up Window Appeared SayingYou Have Got A Male</item>
        <item>Husband says; When I\'m gone you\'ll never find another man like me.\nWife replied; What makes you think I\'d want another man like you!</item>
        <item>When I was young I used to pray for a bike, then I realized that God does not work that way, so I stole a bike and prayed for forgiveness.</item>
        <item>I told my wife that a man is like a fine wine... I always get better with age. The next day, she locked me in the wine cellar.</item>
        <item>Words of a Woman whose husband took extra dosages of Viagra.\nMy Husband has become so horny ..tht I can\'t even yawn in front of him..!!!</item>
        <item>Innkeeper: The room is $15. a night. It is $5. if you make your own bed.\nGuest: I will make my own bed.\nInnkeeper: Good. I will get you some nails and wood.</item>
        <item>In the first year of marriage, the man speaks and the woman listens. In the second year, the woman speaks and the man listens. In the third year, they both speak and the neighbors listen.</item>
        <item>Two woman were talking about the new hunk in the neighborhood.\nBut he acts so stupid, said one to the other. I think he must have his brains between his legs. Yeah, her friend sighed, but I had sure love to blow his mind.\n</item>
        <item>Love thy neighbor all through the day... but first make sure her husband is away!</item>
        <item>Waiter! This coffee tastes like mud. Yes sir, it is fresh ground.</item>
        <item>Wife: Give me some money. I want to buy a bra.\nHusband: Why? You have nothing to put in it!\nWife: You wear shorts!</item>
        <item>What is the best date to bring on a picnic?\nOne who will arch her back so your balls do not get grass-stained.</item>
        <item>It is well known...\nMan stands up to get knocked down, woman lays down to get knocked up.</item>
        <item>What four animals does a woman like to have in her house? A tiger in bed, a mink in her closet, a jaguar in her garage and jackass to pay for it all.</item>
        <item>Boy: Do you like parties?\nGirl: Yes, why?\nBoy: Well then jump in my pants and have a ball!</item>
        <item>Girl: Do you believe in puppy love?\nBoy: I tried it once, but their assholes are too small.</item>
        <item>Boy takes girl into bedroom, pulls down his pants and says meet my little brother\nGirl picks up her bag, on her way out says,call me when he grows up</item>
        <item>A blonde went for hair dresser one day, listening to a walkman.\nThe hair dresser asked her what she wanted, and the blonde replied, I need to get my hair trimmed, just make sure that you do not take these headphones off.\nThe woman looked at the blonde, surprised, but did as she was told. While she was brushing the hers hair, she accidentally bumped the headphones, knocking them to the ground.\nAs she bent down to pick them up, the blonde fell over, onto the floor.\nThe hair dresser was very confused. She picked up the head phones and listened.\nThis is what she heard...breath in...breath out...breath in...breat out...!</item>
        <item>25 useless things in men body :\n- 20 nails that cant hammer\n- 2 nipples that cant produce milk\n- 2 balls that cant bounce\n- 1 Bird that cant fly.</item>
        <item>Yesterday news : An aunty was raped while jogging.\nToday news: More aunties found jogging.</item>
        <item>Signboard outside a prostitutes house:\nMarried MEN not allowed. We serve the needy, not the greedy...</item>
        <item>Judge : Why do u want divorce?\nBanta : She doesnt satisfy me in bed!\nPreeto: Tu yaha ka collector laga hai? Sari colony khush hai, ik tamari agg nahin bujhti.</item>
        <item>Two drunks were walking home along the railway tracks.\nThe first drunk says, There\'s a hell of a lot of steps here.\nThe second drunk says, I ll tell you whats worse, this hand rail is bloody low down</item>
        <item>A lady says to the psychiatrist, I think I might be a nymphomaniac.\nHe says, I ll see what I can do to help you. My fee is eighty dollars an hour.\nShe says, How much for all night?</item>
        <item>Two Muffins were baking in an oven. One muffin turns to the other and says, Holy Shit its hot in here!\nThe other muffin says, Holy Shit... A talking muffin!</item>
        <item>A reporter was interviewing a 104 year-old woman: And what do you think is the best thing about being 104?\nShe simply replied, No peer pressure.</item>
        <item>A couple is lying in bed. The man says, I am going to make you the happiest woman in the world\nThe woman says, I ll miss you.</item>
        <item>One man calls emergency:\n- Come immediately, my little son has swallowed a condom!\nAfter five minutes, the same man calls back:\n- It is OK, I found another one.</item>
        <item>A man is at DMV.\n[DMV Worker] Name, please?\n[Man] Abdul Khan.\n[DMV Worker] S*x?\n[Man] Yes. Three to five times a week.\n[DMV Worker] No, no… I mean, male or female?\n[Man] Both male and female. And, sometimes with camel.\n[DMV Worker] Holy cow!\n[Man] Yes, I did one time with a cow, too.\n[DMV Worker] But isn ´ t that hostile?\n[Man] Horse style, doggy style, any style!\n[DMV Worker] Oh dear!\n[Man] No, no! ….. No Deer…….. Deer run too fast!</item>
        <item>A guy came into a bar one day and said to the bartender, “Give me six double vodka.”\nThe barman says, “Wow! you must have had very bad day.”\n“Yes, I’ve just found out my older brother is gay.”\nThe next day the same guy came into the bar and asked for the same drinks.\nWhen the bartender asked what the problem was today the answer came back, “I’ve justfound out that my younger brother is gay too!”\nOn the third day the guy came into the bar and ordered another six double vodkas.\nThe bartender said, “What the hell? Doesn’t anybody in your family like women?”\n“Yes, my wife…”</item>
        <item>A trucker who has been out on the road for two months stops at a brothel outside Atlanta.\nHe walks straight up to the Madam, drops down $500 and says: “I want your ugliest woman and a grilled cheese sandwich!”\nThe Madam is astonished. “But sir, for that kind of money you could have one of my prettiest ladies and a three-course meal.”\nThe trucker replies: “Listen darlin’, I’m not horny – I’m just homesick.”</item>
        <item>Little Johnny catches his parents going at it. He yells in,Hey, Pop! What are you doin\'?\nHis father says, Son, I\'m filling your mother\'s tank\nJohnny says, Oh, yeah? Well, you better get a model that gets better mileage. The postman filled her this morning</item>
        <item>how would you tell your girlfriend that u want to go to the toilet on u r first date \nHoney, i want to shake hand with my close friend whom i introduce to u later\u0020</item>
        <item>Teacher: Why are you late?\nsharda : One boy was following me, sir.\nTeacher: So, What?\nsharda : That boy was walking very slow.</item>
        <item>Dracula prayed 2 God\nIn my next birth, make me a white angel with wings and still be able to suck blood\nGod granted his wish and made him-\nWHISPER ULTRA!</item>
        <item>What is the difference between snowmen and snowwomen?\nSnowballs.</item>
        <item>Q: What is the height of shock?\nA: When you are having sex with a pregnant woman and suddenly a hand grabs your dick from inside!</item>
        <item>Savitri fought with Yamraj nd got her husband back from death.\nMoral of the story?\nNo one can save you from your wife --- not even Yamraj</item>
        <item>Lionel Messi scores a girl.She ask him to wait, as she changes.\nShe scremes on seeing three men.\nMessi: I m sorry but i cannot perform without Xavi and Iniesta..</item>
        <item>One night a policewoman pulls over a drunk driver.\nShe politely asks him to step out of his car. He willingly does so.\nShe says, Anything you say can and will be Held against you.\nHe replies BREASTS.</item>
        <item>Boy: I saw a dream about you... \nGirl: Awww....\nBoy: You died.</item>
        <item>90yr man: My 18yr wife is pregnant, ur opinion doc?\nDr: Let me tel u a story. A hunter in a hurry, grabs n umbrela instead of d gun. He moves into d jungle, sees a lion, lifts d umbrela, pulls d handle n BANG, De lion drops dead!\nOld man: Dat is impossible, sum1 else must hav shot d lion!\nDr: EXACTLY!!</item>
        <item>4 men were stranded in a desert.\nSuddenly, 1 of them died.\nThe other 3 decided that the only way to survive was to eat the dead body.\nThe 1st man said, I support Liverpool, so I\'ll eat his liver.\nThe 2nd man said, I support Manchester, so I\'ll eat his chest.\nThe 3rd man said, I support Arsenal... but I\'m not very hungry!</item>
        <item>Dear Google, Please stop behaving like my wife. Will you please allow me to complete the whole sentence before you start guessing and suggesting!!</item>
        <item>There are basically 7 TYPES OF GIRLS...\n1. HARD DISK Girls- Remember everything forever.\n2. RAM Girls- Forgets about you the moment you turn her off.\n3. SCREEN SAVER Girls- Just for looking.\n4. INTERNET Girls- Difficult to access.\n5. SERVER Girls- Always busy when needed.\n6. MULTIMEDIA Girls- Makes horrible things looks beautiful.</item>
        <item>Girl: Do you know, why were females created before males?\nBoy: Because God needed a rough funny draft before the final copy!\n</item>
        <item>John: Can you tell me the good way to remember birthday of wife?\nSmith: Its very easy, Just forget it once</item>
        <item>Man: My wife is short of mind and scares of water.\nFriend: How do you know?\nMan: Yesterday, when i reached home and she was in bath tub with the security guard.</item>
        <item>Steve: I have had bad luck with my both wives.\nAngelina: How come?\nSteve: The first wife left me and second one did not!</item>
        <item>Wife: Look at that funny guy who has drunk a lot..\nHusband: Who is he?\nWife: He is my ex-boyfriend but i denied him for marriage.\nHusband: Oh my god! He is still celebrating his freedom.</item>
        <item>Micky: Why women live longer, better and peaceful life?\nAndrew: Because, they do not have a wife!</item>
        <item>Q: What to do to spend happy life with women?\nA: Well, you must love her but do not try to understand her.</item>
        <item>Girl: Do you know, married men live longer than single man do?\nBoy: Do you know married men are a lot more willing to die!</item>
        <item>Human: What is a century like to you?\nGod: It is like a short second.</item>
        <item>Human: What is billion dollars like to you?\nGod: Like a penny..\nHuman: Can i have a penny?\nGod: How funny.. just wait for a second.</item>
        <item>Son: Pl tell me the difference between mom and wife?\nDad: It is so funny, one who brings you into this great world crying and the another ensures you continue crying..</item>
        <item>Patient: What is the cost of plastic surgery?\nDoctor: It is near about 10,000$.\nPatient: Well, what if we arrange the plastic?</item>
        <item>When we are in hospital, our friend asks: How are you dear?\nBut our best friend asks: Hey buddy, how is the funny nurse?</item>
        <item>Son: Dad, What is the secret of happy married life?\nDad replied: It is still a secret!!</item>
        <item>Son: Why do barbers become good drivers shortly?\nFather replied in short: Because they know all the short cuts..</item>
        <item>First friend: Dear, i love lipsticks, they are very tasty.\nNext Day..\nSecond friend: You are liar, i bought 10 lipsticks and ate them.!!</item>
        <item>A man was removing two wheels from his car.\nA girl asked him: what are you doing??\nMan: Can not you see the board, Parking for two wheelers only!!!</item>
        <item>Michal: I have a quiet home life.\nStella: Great, how?\nMichal: She does not speak to me and i do not speak to her..</item>
        <item>Kid: What is husband and wife?\nGranny: Husband is the head of the family but wife is the neck,\nwhich can turn head anywhere!</item>
        <item>Lily: I am giving a big party. Are you coming to attend my 19th birthday party?\nJames: No, i attended that four years ago!</item>
        <item>What is the difference between erotic and kinky?\nErotic = using a feather.\nKinky = using the whole chicken</item>
        <item>Why are men like cars?\nBecause they always pull out before they check to see if anyone else is cumming.</item>
        <item>Wanna hear a dirty joke? A little boy falls into the mud\nWanna hear a clean joke? He takes a bath with bubbles\nWanna hear a dirty joke? Bubbles is Michal Jackson.</item>
        <item>Two eggs boiling in a pan, one male and one female.\nThe female egg says Look, I\'ve got a crack\nNo good telling me replies the male egg I\'m not hard yet</item>
        <item>LadyTeacher: write a sentence ending with hand.\nBanta: My penis in ur hand. Teacher slapped Banta.\nSanta: Sorry mam, I 4got 2 put space betwn PEN IS.</item>
        <item>What is a kiss?\nVery simple, its an enquiry at the top floor about the vacancy in the ground floor.</item>
        <item>Aids awareness slogan:\nCover ur stump b4 u pump dont b silly, protect ur jelly.. AIDS is no joke wrap b4 u poke dont be fool condomize ur tool.</item>
        <item>4 stages of love.\n1. Hand in hand.\n2. Hand in that.\n3. That in hand.\n4. That in that.\nNow don`t ask me what is that.</item>
        <item>On first night both man and wife claim virginity.\nWife: if this is your first time then how you fucked so well?\nMan: if this is your 1st time then how you know I fucked so well?</item>
        <item>Girl enters a sex shop.\nGirl: where is the duplicate penis section?\nClerk: it`s their mam.\nGirl: how much for this big red one?\nClerk: sorry madam, its fire extinguisher.</item>
        <item>Height of laziness: man having sex in train and waiting for the train to jerk.</item>
        <item>Difference between power and stamina?\nPower is when a man can hang a wet towel over his erect penis.\nStamina is to keep the penis erect till the towel dries.</item>
        <item>Banta was travelling in an auto rickshaw with his wife.\nThe driver adjusted the mirror.\nBanta shouted you are trying to see my wife, sit back. I will drive.</item>
        <item>Define rape: rape is not a crime; it`s just a surprise sex.</item>
        <item>Wife: if I sleep with your most loving friend what would be the first thought coming to your mind?\nSmart husband: that you are a lesbian.</item>
        <item>Height of shame: You running with a full erect male sex organ towards a wall and your nose collide first.</item>
        <item>An army got married first night realizes wife having periods.\nHe telegram to HQ: red alert on front extend leave.\nHQ: attack from back and report.</item>
        <item>A girl wears sleeveless dress every time. On right arm she writes `C` and on left arm `L`.\nfriends ask: what does it means? She said: I am cool.</item>
        <item>A sexy and attracted female employee meets her boss and says sir will you remove something from my breast?\nBoss: wow, what?\nGirl: your eyes.</item>
        <item>How to irritate an archeologist? Show him a used whisper and ask him which period it belongs to.</item>
        <item>In a lift, man elbow accidently touched lady`s breast.\nMan: if your heart is soft as your breast you will forgive me.\nLady: if you sex organ is hard as your elbow I am in room 207.</item>
        <item>Man looked his naked body in the mirror says to wife-look 75 kg of pure dynamite. Wife says: but shame on the 5 cm fuse.</item>
        <item>Lady: why is your husband so punctual in returning home from office?\nLady2: I have made a simple rule. Sex will be started at 9pm sharp, whether you are hear or not.</item>
        <item>A man lying on the beach, wearing nothing but a cap over his dick.\nA woman passing by remarks: if you were any sort of a gentle man, you would lift your hat to a lady.\nHe replied: if you were any sort of a sexy lady, the hat would lift by itself.</item>
        <item>There are two things men really like women to do in hurry. Dress and undress.</item>
        <item>Officer: madam swimming is prohibited in this lake.\nLady: then why dint you tell me when I was removing my clothes?\nOfficer: well, that`s not prohibited.</item>
        <item>When a lady s Pregnant, all her Friends touch her Stomach n say `CONGRATS` But, none of them comes and touch men`s Penis and say `Well done` Hard work is not appreciated.</item>
        <item>Teacher: explain responsibility.\nStudent: mam your blouse has four buttons, if three buttons break down the entire responsibility will be on the fourth one.</item>
        <item>Misuse of English: a diagram in a book was not clear. So teacher drew the diagram on the blackboard and announced. Don`t look at the book figure, look at my figure.</item>
        <item>Who is senior? female sex organ or male sex organ?\nAnswer: female sex organ because male sex organ always stands up when he sees a female sex organ, so respects the seniors.</item>
        <item>One man married lady traffic police. Friend asks how your 1st night was.\nHe eplied: She collected Rs.100 from me for over speed, Rs.200 for wrong side entry, Rs.500 for no helmet.</item>
        <item>Contest in a girl`s college: write a short essay which contains religion, sex and mystery.\nWinners essay: oh god, I am pregnant, I wonder who did it.</item>
        <item>A boy wanted to have sex with girl friend ashamed of his small sex organ decided to bring girl friend in dark place opened his zip and put his sex organ on girl friend hands.\nGirl friend: No thanks, I don`t smoke.</item>
        <item>What is the difference between a cricketer and condom? A cricketer drops the catch and a condom catches the drops.</item>
        <item>Who is a true music lover?\nAns: a girl is singing in a bathroom while taking bath and a boy near the keyhole is using his ears and not his eyes.</item>
        <item>Man with no sex organ used a vibrator for years one day wife caught and asked: how dare you cheat me?\nMan: I will explain about the toy, can you explain about kids.</item>
        <item>Sardar was very angry because all jokes were about him; he asked his wife, tell me one joke without my involvement.\nHis wife said: I am pregnant.</item>
        <item>Difference between good girl and bad girl.\nGood girl Open a few buttons in hot atmosphere, but bad girl open all button to make the atmosphere hot.</item>
        <item>During Gandhi times, if aids were known, what would happen? Then the 4th monkey would have kept his hands down.</item>
        <item>Biology class master: all of you draw the male reproductive system.\nStudent: sir please close your zip, girls are copying.</item>
        <item>What`s the difference between hook in cricket and hook of bra?\nOne sends ball out of boundary and another keeps balls within the boundaries.</item>
        <item>Husband: I am going out for five days.\nWife: ok but don`t surprise me by coming back early otherwise you will be surprised.</item>
        <item>Boy and girl of class 2 asked teacher: can kids of our age have kids?\nTeacher replied \u0020NO Never!!\nBoy said to girl : see i told you not to worry!!!!.</item>
        <item>Which is most difficult sport in the world to watch?\nWomen`s doubles tennis- 9 balls bounce at a time and you don`t know which one to watch.</item>
        <item>Son: daddy what`s the difference between confidence and secret?\nDaddy: dear, you are my son that is confidence. Your friend ramu also my son that secret.</item>
        <item>Teacher: What is the difference between Call Girl, Girlfriend and Wife.??\nStudent: Prepaid, Postpaid, Unlimited.</item>
        <item>Girl: If you get a chance,will you marry me.?\nBoy: If I get chance,why would I marry.</item>
        <item>Mom: Why are you pregnant?\nDaughter: This is our project in college about “Miracle of Life”\nMom: Tell me who is he?\nDaughter:I don`t know, it was a group project</item>
        <item>Teacher: why are you late?\nStudent: My dad told me to take our cow to bull.\nTeacher(Angrily): Can`t your dad to it?\nStudent: No, only BULL can do it.</item>
        <item>One Boy To Another,What Did You Do On Mother`s Day?\n2nd Boy,I Tried To Help Few Girls To Become A Mother</item>
        <item>Son – I want a baby brother.\nMom – your dad is overseas.\nWhen he comes back we will talk over it.\nSon – why don`t you give him a surprise</item>
        <item>A Secretary came angrily out of boss cabin\ncolleague asked: What happened?\nShe replied: He asked me are you free tonight?\nI said-yes and bastard give me 50 pages of work.</item>
        <item>Boy (to girl): What`s there in between your legs?\nGirl: Hell! And what`s there in between your legs?\nBoy: A sinner, who wants to go to hell.</item>
        <item>A notice in a factory for girl workers.\n“If your skirt is long, protect yourself from machines at work.\nIf it is short,protect yourself from men at work”</item>
        <item>Medical Science Says:\n“Tight Clothing Slows Blood Circulation”\nBut the Truth is.\n“Tighter The Woman`s Clothing,\nFaster The Circulation Of MAN`s Bl0od”</item>
        <item>Daughter: Mom that man gave me 10 rupees to climb that tree.\nMother: Stupid !He wanted to see ur panty.\nDaughter: I am clever I din`t wear any of them.</item>
        <item>A dentist was caught raping a girl.\nNext day headline, Dentist caught filling wrong cavity.</item>
        <item>Dad watching [F] TV.\nSuddenly his son shows up.\nDad : Gaarib ladkiyaan hai....kapde lene keliye bhi paise nahi haain.\nSon : isse bhi gaarib chahiye toh CD hei merre paas</item>
        <item>Q. What do a gynocologist and a pizza boy have in common?\nA. They can smell it but they cant eat it!</item>
        <item>Q. What did the penis say to the condom?\nA. Cover me im going in!</item>
        <item>Q. What does a guy and a car have in common?\nA. They both have the ability to misfire.</item>
        <item>Q. Whats the difference between a wife and a girlfriend ?\nA. 3 Stone !</item>
        <item>Do you wanna lose ten pounds of ugly fat?\nCut off your head.</item>
        <item>A girl went into a doctors office with a Strawberry up her ass, The doctor said I have got some Cream For that.</item>
        <item>Q. What do a Rubix cube and a penis have in common?\nA. The longer you play with them, the harder they get.</item>
        <item>Q. What does an old woman have between her breasts that a young woman does not?\nA. A navel.</item>
        <item>Q. What is the difference between a woman and a washing machine?\nA. You can bung your load in a washing machine and it will not call you a week later.</item>
        <item>Q. Why did god create Adam before he created eve?\nA. Because he did not want anyone telling him how to make Adam.</item>
        <item>Q. What is a lesbian`s favorite thing to eat?\nA. A Klondike Bar</item>
        <item>Q. What did the elephant say to the naked man?\nA. How do you breath through something so small?</item>
        <item>Q. Why do not women wear watches?\nA. There`s a clock on the stove!</item>
        <item>Q. What doesn`t belong in this list : Meat, Eggs, Wife, Blowjob?\nA. Blowjob: You can beat your meat, eggs or wife, but you can`t beat a blowjob.</item>
        <item>Q. Have you heard about the new super-sensitive condoms?\nA. They hang around after the man leaves and talks to the woman.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s worse than getting raped by Jack the Ripper?\nA. Getting fingered by Captain Hook.</item>
        <item>Q. What do a walrus and Tupperware have in common?\nA. They both like a tight seal.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between a wife and a wheelie bin?\nA. You only have to take out a wheelie bin once a week.</item>
        <item>Q. What did the two lesbian frogs say to each other?\nA. WE DO TASTE LIKE CHICKEN!</item>
        <item>Q. What did the banana say to the vibrator?\nA. Why are you shaking she`s going to eat me.</item>
        <item>Q. What would happen if the Pilgrims had killed cats instead of turkeys?\nA. We`d eat pussy every Thanksgiving.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between love and herpes?\nA. Love doesn`t last forever.</item>
        <item>Q. How do you make your girlfriend scream while having sex?\nA. Call her and tell her.</item>
        <item>Q. A man noticed that his credit card had been stolen but didn`t report it.\nA. The thief was spending less then his wife.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do women have small feet?\nA. So they can stand closer to the kitchen sink.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do men die before their wives?\nA. They want to.</item>
        <item>Q. How do men sort out their laundry?\nA. Filthy, and filthy but wearable.</item>
        <item>Q. Why haven`t they sent a woman to the moon yet?\nA. It doesn`t need cleaning.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between your paycheck and your cock?\nA. You don`t have to beg your wife to blow your paycheck!</item>
        <item>Q. What do you call kids born in whorehouses?\nA. Brothel sprouts.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between a 40 year-old man, and a 40 year-old woman?\nA. A 40 year-old woman dreams of having children, a 40 year-old man dreams of dating them.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s white, smells, and can be found in panties?\nA. Clitty litter</item>
        <item>Q. I married Miss Right.\nA. I just didn`t know her first name was Always.</item>
        <item>Q. Why is psychoanalysis quicker for men than for women?\nA. When it`s time to go back to his childhood, he`s already there.</item>
        <item>Q. How do you know when your cat`s done cleaning himself?\nA. He`s smoking a cigarette.</item>
        <item>Q. Did you hear about the constipated mathematician?\nA. He worked it out with a pencil.</item>
        <item>Q. Who`s the world`s greatest athlete?\nA. The guy who finishes first and third in a masturbation contest.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do men pay more for car insurance?\nA. Women don`t get blow jobs while they`re driving</item>
        <item>Q. Why do schools in West Virginia only have Drivers Ed two days a week?\nA. Because they need their cars for Sex Ed the other three days a week!</item>
        <item>Q. Three words to ruin a man`s ego...\nA. Is it in?</item>
        <item>Q. What is the cheapest meat?\nA. Deer balls, there under a buck.</item>
        <item>Q. How does a guy know if he has a high sperm count?\nA. If the girl has to chew, before she swallows.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s in the toilet of the star ship enterprise?\nA. The captains log.</item>
        <item>Q. What do you call a woman with her tongue sticking out?\nA. A lesbian with a hard-on.</item>
        <item>Q. Did you hear they came out with a new lesbian shoe?\nA. They`re called Dikes. They have an extra long tongue and only take one finger to get off!</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between tampons and cowboy hats?\nA. Cowboy hats are for ass holes.</item>
        <item>Q. What do you say to a virgin when she sneezes?\nA. Goes-in-tight!</item>
        <item>Q. How do you know when you are getting old?\nA. When you start having dry dreams and wet farts.</item>
        <item>Q. What do Disney World n Viagra have in common?\nA. They both make you wait an hour for a two minute ride.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the definition of trust?\nA. Two cannibals giving each other a blowjob.</item>
        <item>Q. Why is it called a Wonder Bra?\nA. When she takes it off, you wonder where her tits went.</item>
        <item>Q. Why don`t women blink during foreplay?\nA. They don`t have time.</item>
        <item>Q. Why does it take 1 million sperm to fertilize 1 egg?\nA. They don`t stop for directions.</item>
        <item>Q. Barking dog at the back door wanting in and your wife`s yelling at the front wanting in. Which one do you let in?\nA. The dog, once he`s in, he shuts up!</item>
        <item>Q. How do you know when your wife is really dead?\nA. Your sex life is the same but your washing pile gets bigger.</item>
        <item>Q. How do you make five pounds of fat look good?\nA. Give it a nipple.</item>
        <item>Q. What do you call two lesbians in a canoe?\nA. Fur traders.</item>
        <item>Q. What do you call a virgin on a waterbed?\nA. A cherry float.</item>
        <item>Q. What does bungee jumping and hookers have in common?\nA. They both cost a hundred bucks and if the rubber breaks, you`re screwed.</item>
        <item>Q. How did Pinocchio find out he was made of wood?\nA. When his hand caught on fire.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s better than a rose on your piano?\nA. Tulips on your organ.</item>
        <item>Q. What did Adam say to Eve?\nA. Stand back, I don`t know how big this thing gets!</item>
        <item>Q. How do you say 69 in Chinese?\nA. Twocanchew (two can chew).</item>
        <item>Q. Why is a woman`s pussy like a warm toilet seat?\nA. They both feel good, but you wonder who was there before you.</item>
        <item>Q. What is the first sign of AIDS?\nA. A pounding sensation in the ass.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do women pierce their bellybutton?\nA. Place to hang their air freshener.</item>
        <item>Q. What is the difference between a clever midget and a venereal disease?\nA. One is a cunning runt, and the other is a running cunt</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between oral sex and anal sex?\nA. Oral sex makes your day, anal sex makes your hole weak.</item>
        <item>Q. What do women and police cars have in common?\nA. They both make a lot of noise to let you know they are coming.</item>
        <item>Q. Why can`t women read maps?\nA. Because only the male mind can comprehend the concept of 1 inch equals a mile.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s a virgin and a balloon have in common ?\nA. All it takes is one prick and its all over.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between your wife and your job?\nA. After five years your job will still suck.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do women prefer old gynaecologists?\nA. Their shaky hands!</item>
        <item>Q. Who can make more money in a week, a drug dealer or a prostitute?\nA. The prostitute because she can wash and resell her crack.</item>
        <item>Q. How are a lawyer and a prostitute different?\nA. The prostitute stops fucking you after you`re dead.</item>
        <item>Q. What is a zebra?\nA. 26 sizes larger than an A bra.</item>
        <item>Q. How does a man show that he is planning for the future?\nA. He buys 2 cases of beer instead of one.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do men find it difficult to make eye contact?\nA. Breasts don`t have eyes.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between a whore and a bitch?\nA. Whore`s fuck everyone at the party, Bitches fuck everyone at the party except you.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between a new husband and a new dog?\nA. After a year, the dog is still excited to see you.</item>
        <item>Q. What do you call it when a 90 year old man masturbates successfully?\nA. Miracle whip.</item>
        <item>Q. What does the receptionist at the sperm clinic say to clients as they are leaving?\nA. Thanks for coming.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the only animal with an asshole in the middle of its back?\nA. A police horse.</item>
        <item>Q. What two words will clear out a men`s changing room quicker than anything else?\nA. Nice dick!</item>
        <item>Q. What is the lightest thing in the world?\nA. A penis...even a thought can raise it.</item>
        <item>Q. Difference between a man buying a lottery ticket and a man fighting with his wife...\nA. A man has a chance at winning at the lottery.</item>
        <item>Q. What is the difference between a bachelor and a married man?\nA. Bachelor comes home, sees what`s in the refrigerator, goes to bed. Married man comes home, sees what`s in the bed, and goes to the refrigerator.</item>
        <item>Q. How do you know when a male porn star is at the gas station?\nA. Right before the gas stops pumping he pulls out the nozzle and sprays it all over the car.</item>
        <item>Q. What did one gay sperm say to the other gay sperm?\nA. I can`t see a thing with all this shit in here!</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the best thing about a blow job?\nA. Ten minutes of silence!</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the difference between sin and shame?\nA. It is a sin to put it in, but it`s a shame to pull it out.</item>
        <item>Q. Did you hear about the guy who finally figured out women?\nA. He died laughing before he could tell anybody.</item>
        <item>Q. Why do only 10% of women go to heaven?\nA. Because if they all went, it would be hell.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the bad news about being a test tube baby?\nA. You know for sure that your dad is a wanker.</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the best part of having a homeless girlfriend?\nA. You can drop her off where ever you want!</item>
        <item>Q. What`s the ultimate rejection?\nA. When you`re masturbating and your hand falls asleep.</item>
        <item>Mama Liberace hollered downstairs, Libby, has that piano tuner come yet?\nNo mama, but his eyes are getting glassy!</item>
        <item>A man had I LOVE YOU tattooed on his dick. He went home and proudly showed his wife. There you go again, trying to put words into my mouth, she said.</item>
        <item>A man and his son were talking about sex.\nThe son asked his father, dad, what does a pussy look like?\nThe dad asked him, before or after sex?\nUmmmm, before sex, the kid replied.\nThe dad said, have you ever seen a beautiful red rose with soft red petals?\nYeah said the son.\nWell, what about after sex? said the son.\nHis dad replied, have you ever seen a bulldog eating mayonnaise!!!</item>
        <item>In the time before time, Adam and Eve had sex for first time ever. After their lustful act was over, Eve went to the stream to clean herself up. As she is washing up, she hears a big booming voice coming from Heavens above.\nFor God\'s sake Eve, how am I going to get that smell out of the fish now?!</item>
        <item>A woman woke up and told her husband of about her last night\'s dream. I was at an auction for dicks. The big ones sold for $1,000 and the tiny ones for $10.\nThe husband says, What about one my size?\nHis wife responds, Didn\'t get a bid, and then laughs to herself.\nThe husband wants revenge, so the next morning he tells his wife about his dream last night. I was at an auction for vaginas. The really tight one\'s sold for $1,000 and the loose ones for $10.\nHis wife says, What about ones like mine?\nThe husband smiles and says, That\'s where they held the auction.</item>
        <item>Two prostitutes were riding around town with a sign on top of their car which said, TWO PROSTITUTES . . . $50.00. A policeman seeing the sign, stopped them and told them they\'d either have to remove the sign or go to jail. Just at that time another car passed with a sign saying Jesus Saves. They asked the cop why he let the other car go and he said, well, that\'s a little different it pertains to religion. So they took their sign down and the next day there they were, driving around town with a new sign which said, Two Angels Seeking Peter . . . $50.00.</item>
        <item>A guy walks into a sperm donor bank wearing a ski mask and holding a gun. He goes up to the nurse and demands her to open the sperm bank vault.\nShe says But sir, its just a sperm bank!\nI don\'t care, open it now!!! he replies.\nSo she opens the door to the vault and inside are all the sperm samples.\nThe guy says Take one of those sperm samples and drink it!, she looks at him BUT, they are sperm samples??? , DO IT!. So the nurse sucks it back. That one there, drink that one as well., so the nurse drinks that one as well.\nFinally after 4 samples the man takes off his ski mask and says, See honey - its not that hard.</item>
        <item>This beautiful woman one day walks into a doctors office and the doctor is bowled over by how stunningly awesome she is. All his professionallism goes right out the window...\nHe tells her to take her pants, she does, and he starts rubbing her thighs.\nDo you know what I am doing? asks the doctor?\nYes, checking for abnormalities. she replies.\nHe tells her to take off her shirt and bra, she takes them off. The doctor begins rubbing her breasts and asks, Do you know what I am doing now?, she replies, Yes, checking for cancer.\nFinally, he tells her to take off her panties, lays her on the table, gets on top of her and starts having sex with her. He says to her, Do you know what I am doing now?\nShe replies, Yes, getting herpies - thats why I am here!</item>
        <item>Q: What\'s the useless skin around a vagina called?\nA: The woman.</item>
        <item>Did you hear about the fellow that was talking to his buddy, when he said, I don\'t know what to get my wife for her birthday. She has everything, and besides, she can afford to buy anything she wants. So, I\'m stumped. His buddy said, I have an idea. Why don\'t you make up a certificate that says she can have two hours of great sex, any way she wants it. She\'ll probably be thrilled! So the first fella did just that. The next day his buddy asked, Well, did you take my suggestion? How did it turn out? She loved it. She jumped up, thanked me, kissed me on the mouth, and ran out the door yelling, \'I\'ll see you in two hours\'.</item>
        <item>A mother is in the kitchen making dinner for her family when her daughter walks in.\n“Mother, where do babies come from?”\nThe mother thinks for a few seconds and says, “Well dear, Mommy and Daddy fall in love and get married. One night they go into their bedroom, they kiss and hug and have sex.”\nThe daughter looks puzzled so the mother continues, “That means the daddy puts his penis in the mommy’s vagina. That’s how you get a baby, honey.” The child seems to comprehend.\n“Oh, I see, but the other night when I came into your room you had daddy’s penis in your mouth. What do you get when you do that?”\n“Jewelry, my dear. Jewelry.”</item>
        <item>A couple were in their bedroom and the girl says to her boyfriend, \'I wish I had bigger tits\'.\nThe boyfriend says \'well what I recommend is to get some toilet tissue and rub it between your tits for 2 months\'.\n\'How will that help to make my tits bigger?\' asks the girlfriend.\n\'Well it worked for your ass\' says the boyfriend.</item>
        <item>Two old people, a man and a woman, walk into a hospital. The doctor says to the old man, I\'ll need a urine sample, a feces sample, and a blood sample.\nThe old man says, What?\nSo the doctor says it again. Once again the old man says, what? So the doctor yells it, I NEED A URINE SAMPLE, A FECES SAMPLE, AND A BLOOD SAMPLE!\nWith that the old woman turns to the old man and says, He needs a pair of your underwear!</item>
        <item>A guy is walking past a bus stop and says to a woman Can I smell your cunt? Fuck off, no you can\'t smell my cunt! the woman yells back at him, Oh he replies, looking slightly confused, it must be your feet then.\nWoman: Can I get Viagra here?\nPharmacist: Yes.\nWoman: Can I get it over the counter?\nPharmacist: If you give me two of them, you can.</item>
        <item>Two lawyers were walking down Rodeo Drive, and saw a beautiful model walking towards them. What a babe, one said, I\'d sure like to fuck her!\nReally? the other responded, Out of what?</item>
        <item>Mother to daughter advice\nMother to daughter advice:\nCook a man a fish and you feed him for a day.\nBut teach a man to fish and you get rid of him for the whole weekend.</item>
        <item>This sex researcher phones one of the participants in a recent survey of his to check on a discrepancy.\nHe asks the bloke, In response to the question on frequency of intercourse you answered \'twice weekly\'. Your wife, on the other hand, answered \'several times a night\'.\nThat\'s right, replies the bloke, And that\'s how it\'s going to stay until our second mortgage is paid off.</item>
        <item>A man walks into a watch and clock store, unzips his trousers and slaps his cock on the counter. The woman behind the counter doesn\'t bat an eyelid. She looks him straight in the eye and says Put that away Sir, this is a clock shop - not a cock shop! Well, replies the man, Why don\'t you put two hands and a face on it?</item>
		<item>Girl: Forgive me father for I have sinned.\nPriest: What have you done my child?\nGirl: I called a man a son of a bitch.\nPriest: Why did you call him a son of a bitch?\nGirl: Because he touched my hand.\nPriest: Like this? (as he touches her hand)\nGirl: Yes father.\nPriest: That\'s no reason to call a man a son of a bitch.\nGirl: Then he touched my breast.\nPriest: Like this? (as he touched her breast)\nGirl: Yes father.\nPriest: That\'s no reason to call him a son of a bitch.\nGirl: Then he took off my clothes, father.\nPriest: Like this? (as he takes off her clothes)\nGirl: Yes father.\nPriest: That\'s no reason to call him a son of a bitch.\nGirl: Then he stuck his you know what into my you know where.\nPriest: Like this? (as he stuck his you know what into her you know where)\nGirl: YES FATHER, YES FATHER, YES FATHER!!!(after a few minutes)\nPriest: That\'s no reason to call him a son of a bitch.\nGirl: But father,he had AIDS!\nPriest: THAT SON OF A BITCH!!!"</item>
		<item>Santa won an English quiz by writing the opposite word of: Manchester United Guess What he has written?.\n\nWoman chest are Divided.. !</item>
		<item>Boy goes to a chemist- "Give me a condom. I\'am going to my gf's house for dinner.Then he says "Give me two more.My gf\'s sis is a bomb \'n her mom is still hot." During dinner, her Dad walks in.Boy lowers his head \'n starts praying.10 min \'n he is still praying, his head down.All are surprised.Girlfriend-" I never knew you are so religious"Boy-" I never knew your DAD IS A CHEMIST!</item>
		<item>A guy had 2 choose a wife from 3 girls.He gave each some money to test them.1st got a makeover to look good.The man got impressed.2nd bought cloths for the guy and told him it\'s he who is prime for her. He liked her also.3rd invested the money and made profit and gave it back. The guy liked her too.And finally when the time came to choose---The guy simply chose the girl with The biggest boobs.\n\nMen will always be MEN!!</item>
		<item>Woman: I had Sex with only 4 boys in my entire life and You had it with 16 Girls, still, Everybody Calls me a SLUT and Call you a REAL MAN,A Winner? Why?\nMan: It\'s because,when a Lock is Opened by many Keys,it Becomes a BAD LOCK.But when a Key Opens many Locks,it becomes a MASTER KEY..</item>
		<item>A boy and girl go for shopping.Girl-(jokingly)- You have nothing in your head then why are you buying a helmet?\nBoy- Yesterday you purchsed a bra, did i ask you anything..?</item>
		<item>On dinner, Son asks father: How many kinds of boobs are here?\nDAD: 3 kinds,In 20s like oranges, round n firm.In 30-40 like pears, still nice but hanging a bit.After 50 like onions, you see them and they make you cry.</item>
		<item>Man says to his wife: Let me take a picture of your breasts, than I can always look at them.\nWife: Let me take a picture of you penis, I will have it enlarged.</item>
		<item>A girl and boy were siting alone,Boy started touching the girl.\nGirl: Don\'t touch me.All thing only after marriage.\nBoy: ok!call me when you are married !</item>
		<item>STRANGE BUT TRUE:-In Ancient Times, In England Before People Havin Sex, They Needed SpeCiaL Permission from the King. People Who Got Permission Used To Hang A Playcard On Their Door Which Said:\nFornication\nUnder\nConsent Of\nKing?\nThats F. U. C. K. For Short.\nNow you Know Where That Word Came From..?</item>
		<item>Q:It\'s the thing that satisfies your mind, body and soul!Do it on bed, on a sofa,in the car or anywhere!\n\nA:It\'s called Prayer! God bless ur naughty mind.</item>
		<item>Q:A short thing its get longer as you hold it and pass between woman\'s breast and enters into a small hole What is it?\n\n Answer: Cars seat belt…you dirty mind.</item>
		<item>Boy: I like the soft thing behind your BRA\nGirl:What?\nBoy:Your Heart\nGirl:I Love the Big thing btween your 2 legs\nBoy:What?\nGirl: Your Bike.</item>
		<item>A pregnant lady went to an astrologer.\nAstrologer:When you deliver a baby, baby\'s father will die.\nLady: Thank god! My husband is safe.</item>
		<item>The most difficult golf course in the world is.\'Women Hole\' any style you play… as many shots you try..and as much perfection you have..you can never get your balls in…!!!</item>
		<item>Q: Why do blondes work seven days a week?\n A: So you don\'t have to retrain them on Monday.</item>
		<item>Q:Who is stronger,Man Or Woman?\nA:A woman because she lifts 2 mountains on her chest while a man lifts 2 stones with the help of a crane.</item>
		<item>A FAITHFUL husband is one who..Always thinks of his wife while sleeping with other Women.Rather than thinking of other women while sleeping wtih his Wife.</item>
		<item>A husband was asked: Do u talk to your wife after sex?\nHis answer: Depends, if I can find a phone.</item>
		<item>Quote For The Day:\n A Girl in Bikini is Like a Loaded Pistol on Your Coffee Table,There is Nothing Wrong with Them,But It’s Hard to Stop Thinking About It.</item>
		<item>Good girls loosen a few buttons when its hot,\nBad girls make it hot by loosening a few buttons!</item>
		<item>There r two typs of HOOKs.\n1st is cricket hook and 2nd is bra\'s hook.\n1st is used to send ball outside the boundry and 2nd is used to adjust balls inside the boundary..</item>
		<item>2 men went to a callgirl.\n1st went in and came out and said "Na.. my wife is better."\n2nd went in and came out and said "You are right ur wife is much better."</item>
		<item>There was a young girl from Wick,who asked her mum what\'s a prick,Her mother said Annie it goes up your fanny and jumps.</item>
		<item>Q: What\'s fashion designing?\nA: Too many brains With too many ideas working on too little pieces of cloth...just to cover two little tits of a model.</item>
		<item>Condom to whisper: Bloody every month you stop my business for one week.\nWhisper: If you make a mistake I lose my business for 9 months.</item>
		<item>Teacher to student: There is two type of sex on earth,Male and female.\nA student: Teacher I know few more.\nTeacher: What?\nStudent: Bedroom sex, bathroom sex and online sex...</item>
		<item>Love is a gamble,Sex is a game,Boyz do the thing Girls get the blame,1 night in pleasure,9 months of pain,1 day in hospital and a junior needs a name</item>
		<item>Son on his honeymoon phoned his mom asking what to do.\nMOM: Put your biggest thing on her hairiest thing.\nSON: Got my nose in her armpit. Now what?</item>
		<item>On a NUDE beach a man shakes hand with a lady and says: I am extreamly pleased to meet you! \nLady: Yeah, I can SEE that!</item>
		<item>Teacher: why are you late? \nStudent: My dad told me to take our cow to bull.\nTeacher(Angrily): Can\'t your dad to it?\nStudent: No, only BULL can do it.</item>
		<item>GOd is great.\nOne such example is here He blows the naughty wind which blows the gal\'s skirt high,But he sends dust along to close the boys eyes as well.</item>
		<item>70 year old man asks his wife Do you feel sad when you see me running behind Girls.?\nWife repiles not at all,even Dogs chase Cars but they can\'t Drive it…</item>
		<item>Boy and girl of class 2 asked teacher:Can kids of our age have kids?\nTeacher :NO Never!!\nBoy said to girl :see i told you not to worry!!.</item>
		<item>Q :Define Gynecologist..\nAns:The only one on the earth who finds problems in the place where all others find pleasure..</item>
		<item>Doctor-Sorry Reports Got Mixed Up I Don\'t Know your Wife Has Aids Or Heart Probx\nHusband: What Should I Do?\nDoctor:Send Her for Jogging Of She Comes Back Don\'t Fuck !</item>
		<item>The Peak economic depression is not noted by the Stock markets readings.. But Merely by the presence of a Spider web In a Prostitute Pussy !!</item>
		<item>Q: Why are condoms transparent?\nA: So that sperms can at least enjoy the scene even if their entry is restricted!</item>
		<item>Any piece of clothing can be sexy..With a Quietly Passionate Woman Inside it.</item>
		<item>Secretry saw her boss\'s pent zip was open,she said sir your garage gate is open.\nBoss:Did you see my Ferrari?\nSecretry:No Sir I Saw a small skuter with two puncture tyres.</item>
		<item>A friend like you is not like boobs, because everyone sucks them.Not like vagina because it tears.You are like a penis because it always stands when needed.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>